[{"id": 5,"language": "Python","multiple": true,"question": "What is the output of the following Python code?\n\nx = [1, 2, 3]\ny = x\nx.append(4)\nprint(y)","options": ["[1, 2, 3]", "[1, 2, 3, 4]", "[1, 2, 4]", "[1, 2, 4, 3]"],"answer": "[1, 2, 3, 4]"}, {"id": 2,"language": "Python","multiple": true,"question": "Which of the following is not a data type in Python?","options": ["int", "float", "boolean", "char"],"answer": "char"}, {"id": 4,"language": "Java","multiple": true,"question": "Which of the following is a valid way to declare and initialize a string in Java?","options": ["String str = 'Hello';", "String str = new String('Hello');", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],"answer": "None of the above"}, {"id": 13,"language": "Python","multiple": false,"question": "Create a Python program that displays integers ranging from 1 to 10, including both 1 and 10. Your program should use a class and include a main method to run the program.","answer": "for i in range(1, 11):\n\tprint(i)"}, {"id": 34,"language": "Python","multiple": true,"question": "Which of the following is not a built-in data type in Python?","options": ["list", "dictionary", "tuple", "stack"],"answer": "stack"}, {"id": 20,"language": "Java","multiple": true,"question": "What is the output of the following Java code snippet?\n\nString s1 = \"Hello\";\nString s2 = \"Hello\";\nif (s1 == s2) {\n System.out.println(\"Equal\");\n} else {\n System.out.println(\"Not equal\");\n}","options": ["Equal", "Not equal", "Compile-time error", "Run-time error"],"answer": "Equal"}, {"id": 35,"language": "Java","multiple": true,"question": "Which of the following is a correct way to declare a multi-dimensional array in Java?","options": ["int[][] myArray = {{1,2,3}, {4,5,6}};", "int myArray[][] = {{1,2,3}, {4,5,6}};", "int[] myArray[] = {{1,2,3}, {4,5,6}};", "All of the above"],"answer": "All of the above"}, {"id": 11,"language": "Python","multiple": true,"question": "Which of the following is not a valid method for removing an element from a list in Python?","options": ["remove()", "delete()", "pop()", "clear()"],"answer": "delete()"}, {"id": 30,"language": "Python","multiple": false,"question": "Create a Python function called multiply_list that takes a list of integers as input and returns the product of all the elements in the list. Call this function from your main program to get the result.","answer": "def multiply_list(numbers):\n result = 1\n for num in numbers:\n result *= num\n return result\n\nif name == 'main':\n my_list = [2, 3, 4, 5]\n product = multiply_list(my_list)\n print(product)"}, {"id": 6,"language": "Java","multiple": true,"question": "Which of the following is a valid way to create a new object in Java?","options": ["MyClass myObj = new MyClass();", "new MyClass() = myObj;", "MyClass = new myObj();", "MyClass myObj;"],"answer": "MyClass myObj = new MyClass();"}]